- Yes, I've written down my number.
- Sure.
Smita ji. Hello.
Myself Kunnu Panjwani.
My friend Jass--
I mean Jasswinder Ahuja,
will be here shortly.
- He'll be here any minute.
- Okay.
But his wife Baani Ahuja,
she's already here.
She's in?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
Hold on, doctor.
I had to tell you something important.
Fixing things between them
will drive you nuts.
- I... I'll see.
- Handle with care.
- All the best.
- Okay.
Glory to Goddess.
Sorry, I'm late.
No, it's okay. Please come.
Thank you.
Couldn't you wait five more minutes?
I was parking--
Can I get you some water?
- Let's start.
- Coffee...
Alright.
Mr. and Mrs. Ahuja.
How long have you two been married?
1825 days. 1825 nights.
Okay, that's... wow!
That's like five years.
Usually husbands don't
remember their anniversary.
And he remembers the exact
number of days and nights.
That's amazing.
- Mrs. Ahuja.
- Yes?
When was the last time
you two were in
agreement with each other?
When we decided to get married.
Oh! That long?
Do you love each other?
I love him.
I love you too, Baani.
But what's the point?
Love alone isn't enough for him.
Day and night he only
wants to get physical.
What's wrong with that?
- It's my right.
- Careful, Mr. Ahuja.
This is your wife we're talking about.
Not some plot of land
you're claiming ownership of.
- No, that's not what I meant.
- No, Mr. Ahuja.
Mrs. Ahuja...
please continue.
Day and night, dawn to dusk...
he's stuck on one thing-
"I wanna make love. Let's go for a quickie.
The bed is calling us, baby. Come on."
But do you ever listen?
Smita ji, my double bed
is living a single life.
The only action it gets
is during an earthquake.
Do you understand?
No, you don't understand.
I'm not denying it, ma'am.
I want to make love.
Full on love to my wife.
But not for love, for a baby!
Baby. Baby. Baby.
Sorry. Give me one second, please.
I am safe. Don't worry.
May I?
I'm not desperate to satisfy my urges.
I just want a cute
little child in my arms.
You don't understand...
my mom is pressurizing me.
People back home think,
I'm a printer that's run out of ink.
What am I supposed to tell them?
Look, ma'am, it's basic biology
babies will be born only
when we do something.
Then what do I do?
Reproduce them on my own?
Enough, Jass!
- Just enough, okay.
- I...
Listen. I never said I don't want kids.
But I'm damn sure
I don't want them now.
And you know what,
this is not working out.
I'm done with you.
- Baani. Baani. Baani.
- Please, don't touch me.
- I wasn't attacking you.
- Mrs. Ahuja...
- What have you done?
- Me?
- You made things worse?
- I did?
I won't pay you.
- What happened?
- Don't pay her.
- Was I supposed to pay her?
- Baani.
- What have you done?
- I did?
You made things worse.
I clearly warned you...
fixing things between them
will drive you nuts.
Jass. Don't jump.
Jass, please.
Baani. Time out.
What are you doing?
Where are you going without me?
You're forgetting that
we share the same address.
We don't need
a marriage counsellor.
Our relationship hasn't
hit a rough patch.
It's just a communication gap, baby.
- Baani. Baani. What are you doing?
- "Love is gold, love is silver..."
Husbands are like Gods,
you don't leave them dangling.
Get off, Jass.
Remember this song?
- "When you're young, love is gonna happen."
- Get off!"
"When you're young--"
Let me in, Baani.
Our future kids are getting crushed.
- Jass.
- Love you.
I hate you!
"When you're young,
love is gonna happen."
Slow down, I'll lose my cap.
What a view.
- Hey, careful.
- Baani, careful.
- Oh God!
- Listen, Baani...
What the-- Baani.
Are you blind?
Girl in a ride, flying high.
Hello, madam.
Please...
Baani, are you going to reverse?
We are not moving our car, mister.
Were you born with this attitude,
or did you order it on Amazon?
Move the car,
or you're going back in a coffin.
Oh... serious.
By the way, you're the one
moving around with coffin bearers.
And I've never backed down,
neither has my car.
Plus, I have lot of time,
the atmosphere is fine.
Let me play some music... online.
Who the hell is this guy?
"It's golden..."
"When you're young,
love is gonna happen."
Bye, girls.
- So long. Love you, girls.
- Bye.
Add me on Insta.
@Boyintheyellowcar.
- Come on.
- Ready?
- Let's go.
- Baani, are you serious?
Come on, Baani.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Have you girls lost your mind?
I asked you to love me...
That girl wrecked my car.
But I am not angry.
Why am I happy?
Wow, excellent. Excellent. Gorgeous.
He's so funny.
What a mood!
I'm in the mood now.
Beautiful. Wow.
Beautiful. Gorgeous.
- Gorgeous.
- Hey, excuse me.
You can't see the moon
without clearing the clouds.
I like that smile.
Hey, Kunnu!
Uncle ji.
- Come here.
- I'm coming.
- I'm coming, baby.
- Baby my foot!
Where the hell is your friend?
The wedding arrangements are ready.
The guests are here.
Where is he?
- The main photographer should be here by now.
- Uncle...
Just relax. Look over there.
Where are you even looking?
Our Jass is right here!
Great. Come on, Jass.
"Everybody knows I'm the baddest.
Who am I without my bad habits?"
"My habits. My bad habits."
"Baby, that's love for me.
All the best things, they come in threes."
"It may seem like a crowd to you.
But to me it's just good company."
Wow. Gorgeous.
How dare they threw the British out.
Bring them back.
"Everybody knows I'm the baddest.
Who am I without my bad habits?"
How many more do you want?
Photos.
- You can take some too.
- Cheap guy.
The father of the bride is fuming.
- How long will I keep covering for you?
- Just a little longer.
Crazy guy.
- Rozario.
- Yeah, baby.
Let me take your picture in the water.
Take good photos?
God's plan. Wow.
Hello ji.
Remember me?
- You!
- Not 'you'...
I have a name. Jass Ahuja.
I am a wedding photographer.
The first meeting is coincidence.
The second time, is God's will.
Don't just stand there. Keep clicking.
Move aside.
I'll click her pictures.
This is my duty.
- Hey...
- Look at me, please.
Chin down... little bit.
Nice. Beautiful. What a face.
Wow...
It's the first time I've clicked the
second most beautiful girl.
I am so good.
And who's the first one?
It's you!
But only when you smile.
- Baani, come on. Let's get ready.
- Baani. Let's go.
- We're getting late.
- I'll go get changed.
Then click as many photos as you like.
You don't need to dress up.
You look cute even in your ID photo.
Are you done? Can we go?
The groom is waiting for us. Come on
What are you doing? Let's go.
She's damn cute, bro!
Make me look slim, okay?
I'll Photoshop you.
Suck your tummy in a little.
Breathe out.
Tummy in, breath out.
Yeah, that's it.
It's okay. Let's go.
Monty ji, smile.
Yes, very nice.
Tummy in.
You don't look like an elephant at all.
Hold your breath.
Hold it, okay.
- Tuck it in a bit.
- Chest out. Yes.
Don't breathe.
Forget you can breathe.
The sherwani just popped a button.
It's okay, Monty ji.
Don't be embarrassed.
It happens all the time.
I have some diet tips for you,
avoid things that make you fat.
- Yes.
- Like... weighing scales.
- Mirrors.
- Yes.
Photos.
And avoid, having
skinny people around you.
I never thought of this, buddy.
Thank you so much.
You're crushing me.
Jass. The bride is ready.
Click her photos as well.
Yes, sir. Coming.
- Your button.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Is there any other option?
- Excuse me. Hi.
- Yes, sir?
Where is the bride's room?
Look, there comes the bride.
Come on, let's go.
Baani.
- Baani.
- Oh, my God. He won't stop.
Baani.
- Kunnu, I just realised something.
- What?
When you love someone
with all your heart...
the universe makes sure
she marries someone else.
What is this crazy girl doing?
- I'll go stop her.
- Yes.
Baani.
What?
If you don't mind,
can I still ask you something?
Ask.
Did you rent out your
eyes to someone else?
What are you doing?
Look at you. And look at him.
Come on, Jass. He's damn cute.
Cute?
Even Balraj's son is cute.
- Balraj...
- My dad.
Alright, if not me, then someone else.
It's not like he's the richest guy.
Jass. Sometimes being cute is enough.
- Kunnu.
- Jass.
This is the world's
shortest love story...
it ended before it even began.
Even the pilot episode of a web series
is longer than this.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
And I'm so lovable!
Cute face, six-pack abs.
If I say anything more, I'll jinx it.
Drink.
What's the point of
these six-pack abs...
when a family pack stole the show?
And guess what,
he's going on a 15-day honeymoon.
What?
15 days... have 15 nights.
And nights are...
No. No, I won't let it be night. No way.
I hate the night.
Kunnu. Throw the ball.
- Be gentle.
- Hey!
Sorry.
Come on, Monty. Pass the ball.
Are you okay?
Bro.
- Come on, guys.
- It happens.
- Kunnu, throw the ball.
- Here we go.
Oh my God.
- Bro...
- Monty, are you okay?
He's okay.
Guys, please play carefully.
What are you doing?
Kunnu... throw the ball.
Kunnu, don't throw the ball.
Here we go.
Hey... have you lost your mind?
What are you doing?
Kunnu, put me down.
Oh, God. Monty.
- Let's get him to a doctor, guys.
- His honeymoon is cancelled.
He broke my nose.
Underground.
What the heck.
What are you guys doing?
We're getting married tomorrow
and you broke my husband's nose.
Husband?
- Baby.
- Baby?
- Hubby.
- Hubby?
- Sweetheart.
- Sweetheart?
Come, we've had enough.
Let's go. Come, my little baby.
- You have a chance.
- I do.
You have a chance to go on a honeymoon.
Hello, Mom. Yes.
The problem you were stressing about?
It's solved.
I've found your daughter-in-law.
Sorry...
What? 'Is she pretty?'
If you see her in a red dress,
you'll give a green signal right away.
Earrings - killer. Anklets - deadly.
Bangles on her wrists Gosh!
I'm in love.
Yes, Mom.
Don't worry. It's a 50% yes.
Yes. Yes.
When did I say yes?
I did.
Just say yes.
50 plus 50 makes 100 percent.
"Killer babe dressed in
Choli flair... international."
"Looks calm,
but she's a storm professional."
"Killer babe dressed in
Choli flair... international."
"Raises the heat by locking eyes,
flirts sensational."
"Get her married..."
"Let's go."
"Get her married... looks really hot."
"Get her married... stays up all night."
"Get her married...
parties all night at the club."
"Get her married..."
"Get her married...
looks really hot."
stays up all night."
"Get her married...
parties all night at the club."
"Get her married..."
"No love for variety
These aunties of society,"
"I love my freedom
That's their anxiety."
"Even my laughter
needs their authority,"
"Grandma's waiting
on the next-gen priority."
"Kitchen duties, that's their policy,"
"Even if daughter-in-law is from IIT."
"How long will daddy's
little angel stay single?"
"Now that we've locked eyes,
let our hearts mingle."
"Daddy's angel flying high, carefree,"
"Come down, baby
Say yes to me."
"Get him married..."
"Get him married...
always window shopping."
"Get him married... pings me on DM."
"Get her married...
he's not thinking straight."
"Get him married..."
"Get her married...
looks really hot."
stays up all night."
"Get her married...
parties all night at the club."
"Get her married..."
Too cool, Jass. Singing and dancing.
- You've got this.
- Thanks, man.
You guys look amazing.
You guys look made for each other.
But it looks difficult.
She won't agree so easily.
Hey, Jass. She's here.
You stay put, dawg.
Listen... Jass...
Moron always chooses
a girl over friendship!
- Hi!
- Do you drink?
- No.
But if you insist, I will.
- Come...
- More.
I said more, dude.
Don't you think you're
overdoing it, Baani?
Shut up.
I'm pretty disturbed
about yesterday anyway.
Why?
Same old... marriage, relationships...
Khosla uncle, Khosla uncle's son.
I don't like it.
I don't like it, dude.
But what are you doing?
Why are you settling for that Khosla
when you've got a
ready-made groom right here?
Is it Jass Ahuja?
It is Jass Ahuja.
Baani, check me out, okay.
I've got a nice personality. Cute face.
I have six-pack abs.
- And... slipping.
- Careful.
lifetime guarantee
to always be by your side.
Will you marry me?
Now.
Now? Are you crazy?
Baani, the future's uncertain.
The wedding altar is
already set for your sister.
- No, no...
- Stop laughing.
Shouldn't the elder sister
get married first?
You are drunk.
Who proposes like this?
Alcohol brings out true feelings.
Come on.
Calm down. Calm down, okay.
I need... I need time, okay.
- You want time?
- Yes.
- I give you time.
- Thank you.
One hour.
One hour?
"One, two, three, four."
"I'll wait an hour,
I'll light the sacred fire,"
"I'll call the priest,
I'll dress the altar."
"I'll wait an hour,
I'll light the sacred fire,"
"I'll call the priest,
I'll dress the altar."
"I'll be the husband, you'll be the wife,
What will that life be like?"
"Can't imagine a better life.
It'll be beautiful."
"Will you marry me?"
Jass. You said one hour.
Six hours have passed.
Where is your bride?
- I don't understand.
- Only owls stay awake at night.
Why are you making me stay awake?
Sir... I am sure my bride will show up.
But when, young man?
Here.
Cool down those raging desires.
She's not coming.
She's probably drunk and
snoring in her AC room.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Really?
Alright, bro.
Come on. Get it over with.
- Pour it.
- Come on.
Sir, start reciting the mantras.
Why? Are you marrying Kunnu?
No...
- Sir...
- What?
- I can feel it.
- Feel what?
My bride's coming.
- My bride's coming.
- Where is she? Where is she?
Turn around!
"My heart's lost in your thoughts."
"Let's get married, the altar's set.'"
"From my side, it's already done,"
"Our pair will be number one."
"I'll walk the rounds,
wear the vermilion bright,
"Exchange garlands, take our vows,"
"I'll be the husband,
you'll be the wife,"
"What will that life be like?"
"Can't imagine anything better."
"Will you marry me?"
What's he doing?
Silence in the court room.
Great.
Amazing.
I've never seen or heard of
a love story, or a wedding like this.
- Kulkarni?
- Yes, sir.
Her family must've figured
out your situation later.
And then what did they do?
My Lord! I took the blows meant for her.
That's okay.
Her family broke all ties with her.
But I stood with her.
And I'm still here for you, Baani.
But you are leaving me.
Mrs. Ahuja,
I don't understand one thing.
Why do you want a divorce
after five years of marriage?
I mean, why?
Is he two-timing you?
No.
Is it a case of physical violence?
- Does he hit you?
- No.
- Doesn't he love you?
- He does.
Then what is the problem?
He loves me too much.
Isn't that great, child?
Absolutely not.
He wants to make love to me all
the time, that too without protection.
Because I want a child, sir.
I want to be a father.
The things I've done
for this relationship...
- you can ask my friend.
- Yes.
Hello, My Lord. Let me tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
Actually...
Why are you wearing a suit?
Why? Doesn't it suit me?
I wear it only on two occasions.
Funerals and divorces.
I'll tell you what happened.
- Go, sit down.
- No, let me...
Go and sit down.
Dresses up in a suit...
You can't imagine what I've
been through In these five years...
What?
Every time I tried to get close...
she
put up a wall between us.
Don't stop me unnecessarily.
When I come close to you, don't stop me.
I am in your bed, I am in your bed.
I... am in your bed,
you're... in your bed.
I missed you, babe.
No, no, no kissing.
Kisses don't get anyone pregnant, silly.
A kiss is where it all begins.
And if you start...
I won't be able to stop.
So why stop? Let's make a baby.
- Come on. Come closer.
- Jass, no.
Jass, no...
Jass... stop it.
No!
A kick?
You actually kicked him?
That's wrong. This is not done.
Do you have any idea what
he would've gone through?
Do you even realize what
a woman goes through in conceiving,
as well as raising up a child?
Sir, to bring a perfect
child in this world,
one has to be a perfect mother.
And currently,
I'm the CEO of a company.
I want to focus and dedicate
all my time to my career.
I want to be mentally
and physically prepared
in bringing up our kid.
But for now...
I'm not ready.
You want a child,
but you don't.
You want this marriage,
Therefore, the court will keep
this divorce case
in a lock-unlock
category for six months.
This period is granted,
so that the couples who have
taken this significant step
can reflect and be certain
whether it's the right decision.
For now, I will strike
the gavel to separate you.
But something tells me...
you'll find your way back to each other.
The court is adjourned.
Mr. Jasswinder Ahuja.
You've been the nicest man I know.
And you'll always be the
proudest chapter in my life.
It's alright.
Sometimes things don't work out in life.
It didn't work out between us.
Jass...
let it go.
Move on.
And I wish you
all the best for your future.
Can I hug you?
Please.
Of course.
What happened?
Am I crazy or
is that the same bottle
we drank from and got married?
It's the same brand, right?
Yeah, that's the same bottle
that made our heads spin.
And had us circling the
holy fire to get married.
Oh, God.
How will we divide the bottle now?
- Oh...
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
No.
- Truth or dare? Truth or dare?
- No, guys. I can't.
This is such a silly game.
Can't we play something else?
- Truth or dare? Truth or dare?
- Okay, okay, okay.
Dare.
Yes.
See that handsome
photographer over there.
- Where?
- With the camera.
Henry, she's your wife, not your cousin.
Look at her with more love, mate.
And, Hanna, just stroke his beard.
Yes. That's lovely.
Nice and soft. Great.
Be still.
Go and kiss him.
What?
- Go and kiss him.
- No.
She can't kiss a stranger. I agree.
- He's so cute. He's so cute.
Very nice.
My marriage didn't last five years,
Looks like theirs will end in five days.
Hey... I swear, you won't
last five seconds in this world.
"Two times the tax. For God's sakes."
You know Hindi. Very nice. Very nice.
Sorry. Sorry.
We'll get some photos
clicked on that bridge.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Come on, honey.
Come, goatee and gal, let's go.
- You can.
- No.
Don't let go of the rope.
Keep paddling.
Paddle. Paddle.
Don't let go of the rope.
Help.
Help! Help!
Somebody help me.
- Somebody help me.
- She will drown.
- Please help.
- Vicky, help her.
Help. Help.
Help.
- Thank God.
Wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
Breathe, breathe!
What do I do? What do I do?
Wait... only one man can
save her in this situation.
My school headmaster, Mr. Shukla!
Sir, what do I do?
Well... when things go wrong,
or someone's in trouble,
or can't breathe...
you give them CPR.
First, lock your hands,
place them on the patient's chest...
and pump at regular intervals.
Pump... pump...
Thank you, Mr. Shukla!
pump, pump, pump...
Oh no...
It's not working, Mr. Shukla!
Say something!
Else, this beautiful girl will die!
How can I let her die?
Mr. Shukla won't let her die.
Step two of CPR -
hold her nose
and blow air into her mouth.
How?
Like this.
What's so funny?
I'll try...
Sorry, ma'am...
- Like this, Mr. Shukla?
- You're not supposed to kiss her.
You're supposed to blow air!
Okay.
Hallelujah!
It's a miracle.
Are you okay?
Do you want water?
No... sorry no water!
Are you okay?
Oh, my God. She did it.
No, she's still doing it.
Please, someone stop her.
Preet, that's enough.
Thank you.
I didn't get a chance
to say it the other day.
You're lucky I found you today.
Hey. Your money.
That's for you.
The value of my kiss is only £5?
Rise and Shine. Vodka and Wine.
Reach Club Dance and Dine...
before Nine.
Fine...
Fine!
Chug. Chug. Chug.
Come on, Preet.
Woohoo!
Chug. Chug. Chug.
Whoa!
"Oh my God."
"Oh what."
"Twerk it."
"Shake it. Shake it."
"Oh my God."
By the way,
are you single?
Fully single.
Okay. I'm gonna go
get another drink then.
One more?
Is she a drunkard?
Works for me.
Move.
- Sir, it's mine.
- Bro, it's mine.
- It's my tip.
Sir, it's mine.
I double the tip, okay.
Sir, Indian money?
You're not British either.
Take it and leave.
Use force, but make no fuss.
Come to the bedroom,
follow the red door.
Move aside.
Villages have homes...
but this home has an entire village.
They are loaded.
Oh!
Tommy is a good boy.
Who's a good Tommy?
You're a good Tommy.
Bad Tommy.
No, Tommy. No.
Tommy. Tommy.
I don't want rabies. I want babies.
Why are you getting angry?
Is it because I called you Tommy?
Your madam called me.
Let me go.
I'll go.
Who's going to save me now?
My PT teacher... Mr. Mishra.
Youngsters
kids my height,
take a deep breath before you run.
Put your chest out,
keep your posture straight.
And keep your eyes on
your 'disha' (direction) while running.
Understood?
Hi, Disha.
Wrong.
Not this Disha.
I mean direction, your goal.
So that you can stay ahead
and leave everyone behind.
- Sir, what if a dog chases us?
- Good question.
If a dog chases you, don't think
just run. Long strides, big leaps.
Okay, Mr. Mishra... I'll try.
Here is the dog.
Hey, dog! Hey, dog!
Mishra sir! Mishra sir!
- Long strides! Big jump!
Long leap!
Climb a wall! Climb a tree!
Be like Spider-Man!
I'm climbing. I'm trying.
Climb whatever you get.
But save yourself from the dog!
I've climbed up, Mr. Mishra.
I'm safe.
Follow the red...
Red door.
Red door. Red door.
Red door?
Eenie, meenie, miny, moe...
Two red doors,
which one do I go?
Damn it.
What the hell.
Preet.
Cutie.
Perfume.
"Two hearts are meeting quietly,
in secret."
Don't kill me.
Don't sell my kidney, please.
- I am very young. Please.
- Get up.
My mother is still alive...
Do you even know whose
house you've barged into?
For your information -
Jogi Randhawa.
He doesn't talk much...
his gun does the talking.
Gun?
Sir, sorry.
I haven't done anything, please.
- I haven't done anything.
- Jass?
- Preet. Save me.
- Brother...
Brother?
What are you doing, brother?
You're scaring him. Stop it.
Jass is--
Truth or Dare?
Are you two addicted
to this game or what?
Cheating. Cheating. Cheating.
This is cheating.
You've already done the dare.
Time for the truth.
Tell me... what were
you doing in my house,
in my sister's room...
so late at night?
You sister called me.
She said, 'using force
without the fuss, enter the red door.'
I know Preet from before, sir.
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
I saved her life.
Actually, Shukla sir solved the matter.
- Who is Shukla sir?
- My school headmaster.
I did exactly like he said.
I went close to her and kissed her.
- Sire.
- I mean... I gave her oxygen, sir.
O2.
What is he saying?
Explain it to your brother.
Yes, brother.
Remember what happened in Uttarakhand?
I almost drowned while rafting.
He's the one who saved me.
I am alive because of him.
Sire, does saving her life give
him the right to enter her bedroom?
Brother...
Look.
She scribbled the address on
this note and called me here.
It was her.
Your dogs even chased me.
But Mishra sir solved that matter.
Who is this Mishra now?
My PT teacher, sir.
Stop this Mishra-Shukla nonsense.
Just tell me whether
you love Preet or not.
Growing love, sir.
Growing...
Every second I fall
more in love with her.
Oh.
And what about you, Preet?
Do you too have a growing love for him?
No!
- What?
- What are you saying?
Your brother's going to shoot me.
I mean, we just met.
I want to get to know him.
I mean... he's cute.
Cute? Okay, fine.
You, boy. Come here.
No, no.
- Go on.
- Come on.
- Go.
Don't push.
Come on.
Don't even think of betraying her.
Cross a Randhawa,
and you're done.
That chance, I'll give you none.
Soon, wedding prep will have begun.
Preet, let's get some fresh air and fun.
And listen, idiot.
Next time you want to meet Preet,
don't jump across the wall.
Use the main door.
Alright, I'll use the main door.
Keep the door open.
Thank you, brother.
You're a sweetheart.
- Need your blessings.
- Let's go.
Where are we going?
Sire, I feel--
Growing love.
"Forgetting all the
worries in the world,"
"I drift closer to you..."
"Forgetting all the
worries in the world,"
"I drift closer to you..."
"In your eyes,"
"I find my light."
"And be yours forever."
"I'm yours..."
"Are you a dream,
or are you my destiny?"
"It's hard to believe"
"I deserve your love,
I want to believe."
"Are you a dream,
or are you my destiny?"
"It's hard to believe"
"I deserve your love,
I want to believe."
"Nothing matters more
than me being yours."
"Say what's in your heart,"
"so I can finally sleep in peace."
"And be yours forever."
"I'm yours..."
"Be yours."
"Everybody knows I'm the baddest.
Who am I without my bad habits?"
"I just play it too much,
I don't plan it."
"Rolling stone better
keep it them balance. Please."
"Baby, that's love for me.
All the best things, they come in threes."
"It may seem like a crowd to you.
But to me it's just good company."
"Not a player I'm the whole
game the worst of them all."
"Way over this time
I might have gone too far."
"I been going' hard
it's just who you are."
"They love me I'm leavin'
I shoot like a star."
"When you're young..."
Squeeze me.
Hi.
- Baani?
- Yes, Baani.
Won't you ask me to come in?
Remember, I'm still your wife.
Yeah, come in.
- Wow, it's a beautiful house.
- Thank you.
Old habits die hard.
By the way, what are you doing here?
Are you here with the divorce papers?
No. I want to tell you something.
You could have called.
I couldn't have told you on the phone.
It's personal.
- Jass, are you ready?
- I am.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Stop spinning me around.
Tell me what happened.
I'm pregnant.
Wow. Congratulations.
Who's the boy?
What do you mean, who's the boy?
Are you for real, Jass?
Is this all you have to say,
who's the boy?
- No...
- You don't remember, do you?
Let me remind you.
Remember, the judge said he
would decide our future in six months.
I went home and I was packing
and you saw that bottle.
Remember, Jass...
we just kept drinking that night.
And eventually... the alcohol took over.
Then... you came close,
like you always do...
and I raised my leg to kick you,
like I always do.
But then...
Now you remember who's the boy?
Yes.
Jass, you're going to be a father.
This is exactly what you wanted.
Oh my God.
Yeah. Oh my God.
Only God can plan this for us.
But what about your goals? Aspirations?
Your self growth as a woman?
- It's okay.
- You're a fighter.
- Really?
Jass, God has given me the opportunity
to become a mother for the first time.
I'll sort out my career.
I'll work from home.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
Everything happens for a reason.
In our case, it's for the kid.
You and me will bring
a third person in this world.
- Jass.
- Enough.
No one will come between us.
"Toasted. Toasted. Toasted."
- Sorry.
- Jass?
But it's... switched off.
The battery is dead.
I'll put it to charge.
- Hello?
- Baby, come quickly to my house.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
If you don't come,
then I'm coming there.
- No... no, no, no...
- Okay.
No. No. No...
Jass. Jass. You forgot your pants.
I know, Martha!
And guess what...
I forgot to wear a condom too!
Preet.
Jass.
You said it's something urgent.
All good?
First you tell me,
why are you in your shorts?
You said it's an emergency.
Now, tell me what happened.
Ready?
Okay.
Wait a second? Do you have COVID?
- No offence, please.
- Jass.
Look at it properly.
Maintain two feet distance.
- Please.
- Don't you know what this is?
It's a pregnancy test kit.
Jass, I am pregnant.
I'm pregnant.
Jass...?
No, this can't be happening.
What do you mean can't be happening?
It's happening. It's real.
I'm pregnant.
But I used protection...
So? Protection failed.
How can protection fail?
Protection's job is to protect.
I have just given you such great news,
and you're not happy.
You're not happy.
I'm happy.
Jass, you're going to be a father.
This is exactly what you wanted.
I am very happy.
Look at my face.
See how happy I am.
I am very happy.
But these condom companies,
I won't let them off so easily.
I will file a case against them.
I will sue them.
How can they do this?
Instead of being happy about the news
you're angry with the condom company?
- Not cool.
- I am angry with myself.
No, it's fine. It's okay.
Just let it be.
- It's okay.
- I'm lost...
I'm lost... for words.
You're not happy.
Very happy.
You and I will bring
a third person into this world.
- Jass...
- Enough...
no one will come between us now.
- And guess what?
- What?
Today is International Pregnancy Day.
What are the odds?
Brilliant. Brilliant.
What a day.
So everyone's going
to announce - I'm pregnant.
We are all pregnant.
You're so funny.
For the next nine months
it's going to be
anxiety, depression, mood swings...
Labour pain as well.
Plus, it's also going to kick.
But where are you going?
I'm going to the temple
to bang my head...
I mean, take blessings.
Don't stop me.
We've to tell my brother.
He's gonna be so happy.
'Jass, I'm pregnant.'
"Toasted. Toasted. Toasted."
- Mom.
- Jass, what happened?
Is everything alright?
Mom, God has answered your prayers.
I'm, stuck between two.
Now, two are on the way. Two.
I didn't understand, son.
- Mom.
- Hello?
Hello... Hello Jass?
Twinkle, twinkle... double the worry,
How am I going to handle
two love stories?
This is the limit! Unbelievable!
First, you couldn't even have one baby.
Now you're having two!
What crappy luck!
Why are you hitting me?
Tiny. Tiny.
How can I help you, Mr. Kunnu?
My friend is under a lot of stress.
Give him today's special.
Sure, sir.
In today's special, we have
a double cheese burger,
a double sundae
and a chilled glass of beer.
Double? Double. Double?
Do you know, my life's biggest trouble
is because of the word "double".
- Huh?
- Yes.
I have "double" the girls in my life,
and while dealing with them,
I'm going to have "double" kids now.
And now you're...
offering me double-double?
Bloody double balloon!
I double curse you!
May you catch double the disease!
May you go home, and find out
you have double fathers.
- That's right, double fathers.
- Huh?
Stop, Jass. Jass.
Damn, are you made of double cement?
Let go of me!
- Bloody fatso.
- Stop insulting him now.
I'll insult him double the times!
Mr. Kunnu, this guy is a crazy guy.
He's a psychopath.
Take him out of the club,
or take him out of the UK.
Sorry, Tiny. Sorry.
What, "sorry Tiny?"
- His name is Tiny?
- Just sit down.
Drink this.
What's wrong with you?
Sorry.
Don't get stressed.
Preet.
Hi, Jass.
Hi.
Who is she?
She...
Preet, I'm Baani.
I was in Jass's life before you.
And we were married to each other.
He wanted a baby, and I didn't.
So we separated, but...
now I'm carrying his baby.
Jass told me about--
My brother only holds a gun,
but I fire.
What are you doing, Preet?
Have you lost your mind?
Preet, you're making
a big mistake by killing him.
You're right.
I should kill you.
Baani!
Baby, are you okay?
What happened?
Why did you suddenly fall down?
No, I...
Dizziness and loss of balance
is common during pregnancy.
I'm the one who is pregnant.
Not you.
- Yeah.
- You're so funny.
Hey...
My brother!
I gave you permission
to go out with Preet.
But before marriage,
you've made my sister--
Sorry, Randhawa ji.
I should've asked permission.
It was a mistake made out of love.
Don't even think about doing it again.
Babies... should be born out of love.
So understanding.
Sire, the priest is here.
- Please come.
- The priest.
But why is the priest here?
Sir, have you found an auspicious day?
Oh, an auspicious date for the
baby's 'Naamkaran' (naming ceremony).
In fact, I think we
should name the boy Karan.
'Naam Karan'. Get it?
Good one.
The priest is here to
pick a date for the wedding.
Wedding? Whose?
Ours. Who else?
- Okay.
- Tell us, sir.
The first eight days
of next month are auspicious.
- Great.
- But I am not free.
- Are you busy?
- I am conducting several weddings.
- Brother.
- Guggi.
- Sire...
- Cancel all his weddings.
Sire.
There you go, sir.
Your schedule is clear.
Second marriage before
divorcing your first wife?
I'm the judge,
and I'll sentence him.
Death sentence!
This wedding is not possible.
This wedding is not possible at all.
Why? Are you busy as well,
just like the priest?
- Let me explain.
- Explain.
Randhawa ji, you must've
attended your father's wedding.
- You fool.
- Brother.
How can anyone attend
their father's wedding?
Exactly, sir.
That's what I am saying.
Fate is giving my child the
chance to attend my wedding, sir.
Just visualise, sir.
Happy family in one frame, sir.
Nephew Randhawa in uncle Randhawa's lap.
And our child, happy in a nappy,
will sing and dance.
Uncle and nephew spinning
around in the city of London.
Spinning... Spinning...
Enough!
Excellent!
Even the filmmaker Sooraj Barjatya
never had a vision like this.
It's an original idea.
What do you say, Preet?
Yes, I like it.
- You're happy, I'm happy.
- I like it. I'm happy.
It is decided.
First, the baby comes in a carriage,
then we'll dance at the marriage.
Right... uncle and nephew spinning
around in the city of London.
- Spinning.
- Spinning... Spinning...
- Bye.
- Bye, baby.
- Just call Jass.
- Baani.
Baani.
- What happened?
- She's in terrible pain.
- Hurry, take her to the hospital.
- Thank you, Martha, thank you.
- Take her to the hospital quickly.
- Careful.
Come, come.
- Are you okay, Baani?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
The hospital is nearby.
Baani, I want to tell you something.
Yeah.
I mean, I can tell you this later,
but I can't keep this inside me anymore.
When we separated...
you told me to move on.
Months later, I met a girl.
Preet.
We fell in love, Baani.
Baani...
Baani, are you listening...
What the hell!
But that's--
Sire, it's Jass...
your brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
- What?
- Jass?
Where is Jass going?
Who's honking here?
Randhawa? Where did he appear from?
Always bloody after me.
Sire, why is he driving so fast?
- Call him. Call him.
- Yes.
"Toasted. Toasted. Toasted."
He didn't answer, sire.
Call him again.
- 'The number you've called is switched off'
- It's okay.
Sire, it's switched off!
Sir, I'm a vegetarian,
but still I smell something fishy.
Just shut up, Guggi.
Brother. Speed up.
I'm feeling very, very uneasy.
Just take a deep breath, okay.
Who gives such people
a driving license?
Why did you stop, sire? Let's go.
This is London, not Ludhiana.
Damn!
We made it. We made it.
We overtook everyone
and made it to the hospital first.
Baani, wake up.
Come on, come on, fast.
Let's go, Baani.
Jass, I can't walk.
Don't worry.
We've reached the hospital.
- Let's go inside.
- Hold on.
Don't get stressed.
Selfie Kumar is here.
Sit. Sit down.
- Sir, where is the doctor?
- Wait a minute.
Are you the husband?
- Yes.
- Is she the wife?
- She's pregnant.
- That's life.
- Wait a minute.
- What are you doing?
Virtual registration.
Everything's digital now.
Now it's safely stored on my phone
that you're the husband
and she's your wife.
- Sir, we want to see the doctor...
- Hold on.
Sophie. Take the patient to Dr. Gulati.
- Please.
- Come.
Excuse me. Mr. Ahuja.
That's me, sir.
- Myself Dr. Gulati.
- Hi.
How is Baani?
Not Baani. A story, honey...
The story of a mother.
A mother carries her child
for nine months in her womb,
three years in her arms,
and a lifetime in her heart.
That's right, sir.
But please tell me how is Baani.
She's not Baani. She's love, honey...
A mother's love.
When a child kicks in the womb,
a mother's heart jumps with joy.
Sir, please tell me, how is Baani?
Why are you talking
about all this nonsense?
How is Baani?
Mr. Ahuja, relax.
Religiously speaking,
you should read these three books.
'Maa ki Mamta' written by Mamta's mother.
('A Mother's Love' written by a Mother)
My favourite...
'Nau Mahina With My Hasina'
(Nine Months With My Beloved)
And... 'Lalla Lalla Lori, Do Patang Ek Dori'
(The Lullaby Of Two Kites And Their String)
I've written this myself.
Listen, doctor.
I'm not here for an exam.
I've lost my patience.
- Did I ask you before becoming a father?
- No.
I am going to meet Baani.
I'm not asking you,
I'm telling you this.
Excuse me...
- Mr. Ahuja...
- What now?
Idiot.
He's definitely not ready
to become a father.
Your baby is fine.
Earlier, I didn't want a child, Jass.
But now, when this child
is coming into this world,
this child is my entire world.
Go to the cafeteria, Baani.
I'll join you in a bit.
Jass?
Brother.
I need to use the restroom.
Okay, go.
Alice, just come with me.
Let's go.
Oh... Oh, my God. Sorry.
What are you doing here?
Shitting.
Can you close the door?
Brother-in-law,
we've been waiting for a long time.
Come on, tell us.
Tell you what?
You were racing down the road,
you didn't hear us honking,
didn't answer the phone,
and even switched it off.
What's going on, brother-in-law?
Brother... truth is...
I love someone else more than Preet.
- What?
- Yes.
It's true.
Preet's happiness.
Her happiness.
She should get the right doctor,
right hospital, top-class treatment.
That's why I got here before you did.
- Jass.
- Yeah.
Do you see everything I'm doing for you?
- See, brother. He loves me so much.
- Yes.
- Mrs. Preet Randhawa?
Dr. Gulati is ready for you.
- He's calling you in.
- Let's go.
You guys sit here.
- You stay here.
- Okay.
Move him aside and come.
One second. Jass.
- Please come.
- Be careful.
This way, please.
I'll be back.
Everything is normal.
- Thank God.
- These minor pains
are normal during pregnancy.
By the way, where's the baby's father?
- He--
- Doctor. I am here.
You can see me.
I am the father.
Many congratulations.
- Thank you.
- But why have you covered your face?
Any worries?
No worries. It's a father's story.
Like a mother, a father also
watches his child grow for nine months.
He rocks him in his
arms for three years.
And loves him from
the bottom of his heart for a lifetime.
Birdie.
- How sweet.
- Wow.
These words sound familiar.
No, no... it's about a father's glory.
Sacrificing all his desires,
a father showers all
his love on his child.
What?
A father's love just like
a mother's affection.
I'm shocked to hear this.
- No, no...
- Then?
It's a father's glory.
When the child kicks
in the mother's womb,
a father's heart also
jumps with joy.
By the way, according to ChatGpt,
every father should
read these three books.
'Daddy Daddy Ho Jao Ready'
(Daddy, Daddy Gear Up Already)
'Volume Bandh Kar, Pappa Jag Jayega'
(Turn Down The Volume Or Daddy Will Wake Up)
And 'Who's Your Daddy Now?'
Wow, emotionally speaking,
I've never seen a more responsible
father than you in my life.
I've never seen one either.
And you never will.
I just met a new father.
He was so badly behaved and rude.
- Oh no.
- And look at him.
It seems like you're the
one expecting, not your wife.
Except, I'm from Chandigarh, sir.
- How is my child?
- Godamba.
Godamba. Go... Go...
- Hello, Godamba.
- Come.
I am sorry, Godamba.
Are you alright? You rest.
You rest now.
You are talking so much.
My phone.
Got you.
Jass dude.
There are three types
of mills in the world.
Textile mill.
- Treadmill, and...
- Hey... Please...
'Bahar aake Mill'
(Meet Me Outside)
You lock eyes, then play shy...
a spell cast by you.
Two wives, two babies...
All belong to you!
- Jogi Randhawa--
- Softly.
Jogi Randhawa kills anyone
who betrays him.
What do you want?
Blessings. Because I know what's going on.
God bless you. Bye.
My entire family will bless you.
For your family.
I have a big family. Very big family.
I am a poor guy too.
With two wives.
Proud of you, Jass.
What crappy luck.
Both of them go to the same hospital.
Same doctor,
and now, the nurse is blackmailing you.
And that violent Randhawa...
if he finds out, he'll throw
you in that hospital's morgue.
Unbelievable.
What are you doing?
Where are you going now?
Where?
Back to my country. My motherland.
I'll be safe and secure in my country.
Message or no message,
I'll go back home.
All the best to you.
Well done, man.
- You want to leave, right?
- Yes.
Fine. Leave.
But tell me one thing.
Who stood beside you every time
you got in trouble?
- My mother.
- Other than that?
It was Jass Ahuja.
Remember your girlfriend?
- Chinky?
- Yeah, Chinky.
When her father would
chase you with a stick,
who took your share of the beating?
Jass Ahuja.
- Jass, sorry.
- It's okay.
But one thing is bothering me.
What?
I hope Baani and Preet
don't come face to face.
No chance.
Never.
This is London. Not Dadar station,
where Baani and Preet
will bump into each other.
I know you mommies must be super excited
to bring that special one
in your lives.
But do you know, according to research
one in ten men cheats
on their wives during pregnancy.
For two major reasons.
First, denial of sex.
And the second,
the case of an unexpected child.
The sudden news of a child's arrival
feels like a burden to the father.
And cheating lightens that burden.
I think, at Riverstone Hospital...
- Oh yeah, I remember seeing you there.
- Yeah.
What she was
saying about husbands...
Thank God my husband isn't like that.
Mine neither.
- I'm Baani.
- Hi Preet.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Husbands can cheat with anyone.
A pretty neighbour,
hot office secretary,
or even the house help.
Yeah. Men are crazy.
House help?
- Alice.
- No.
We won't get a better chance.
Your madam's outside, and we're inside.
- Sir...
- This sir wants to rest... on your chest.
- No, sir.
What no?
I haven't touched Preet
or anyone else in four months.
Sir, please stay back.
I think the Bhediya (wolf)
inside you has woken up.
Bhediya?
Why does everyone want
to turn me into a bhediya?
Don't think I can't control myself.
I can, Alice.
But what do I do
about my hormones?
My hormones refuse to calm down.
Come here.
- What comes after 12?
- 13?
I've been falling for you
since we met.
I'm losing myself.
Jass!
What happened?
- Get up.
- I'm confused.
Who is it so early in the morning?
There aren't even milkmen here.
Hi.
- Jass?
- I'm opening.
- Yes, I'm opening.
Preet, what a surprise.
- Jass, what the--
- What brings you here?
- Let's sit down.
- Move.
What happened, baby?
Jass, I've decided.
- What?
- I'm moving in with you.
- Have you lost your mind?
- Excuse me?
What made you suddenly
decide this, crazy girl?
And even if you did,
why now, all of a sudden?
- Why do you keep looking that side?
- Where?
Is someone in the bedroom?
- Not there...
- So someone's in the bedroom.
I don't even sleep in the
bedroom myself. I sleep here.
Preet. Preet. Preet, please.
Suspicious, suspicious,
what the--
Do you believe me now?
Don't you have another bedroom?
- Yes, so?
- Move.
Am I broke!
Should I sleep on the street?
Jass. I knew it.
Who is this girl?
Him. This is my karma
for my past sins.
- Get up.
- What are you doing?
Kunnu?
- Preet.
- Kunnu...
What is she doing here?
Kunnu, Preet thinks
you're my cuddle bunny.
Nonsense.
I'm sorry, but...
he has very girly legs. No offence.
Okay, I need to freshen up.
- Come, let's go to your bathroom.
- Yeah, come.
Hey!
Crazy,
I mean, the ambience is crazy good.
The weather is romantic...
And you're wearing Dolce and Gabana.
Baani. Baani.
- 'Paani'.
- Right.
The 'paani' (water) is not flowing.
The pipelines.
You should shower over here.
The flow is awesome.
Fresh water from the Thames.
Go. Live your best life.
Shampoo. Enjoy.
Bathe the baby too,
make it a baby shower!
Baby shower. Come on Let's go.
- The water's really nice.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What should I do?
- Preet over here. Baani over there.
What do we do now?
Baani!
- Baani, is here...
- This bag, purse? Whose are they?
- Whose are they?
- Whose?
Whose are they?
Whose are they? Whose are they?
- Whose are they?
- They're his.
Ouch. They're mine.
Suits me, right?
Since when do you
use a purse, Kunnu?
Actually, Baani...
lately, I can feel
some changes in myself.
What do you mean?
I ignored it at first.
But now I'm sure,
there's a girl inside me.
Yes, there's a girl inside him.
That's why the lady's purse,
Barbie shorts,
waxing, manicure, pedicure...
And now I even want to
get a tattoo on my lower back.
Any suggestion, guys?
- Any?
- Butterfly?
But what if it flies away?
- Naughty. You've become naughty.
- Oh God.
You need a reality check.
And I need a coffee.
Scoundrel.
Sweetheart, I'll get the coffee.
You go and rest. Baby needs rest.
Walk carefully. Don't come back.
Where do I go?
I'm stuck in the middle!
- Preet!
Kunnu, why are you holding my bag?
- He is keeping your bag in the room.
- Yes.
Bag, take Kunnu inside.
- I mean, Kunnu, take the bags inside.
- Yes.
Is that for me?
- How sweet.
I am also yours.
I'm coming inside.
- Come.
- Love you. We need some alone time.
Miss you already.
I'm in this mess because of you.
The things you make me do...
- Jass...
- Baani!
- Where's my coffee?
- Coffee? Kunnu finished it.
What?
Yeah, Baani,
actually your coffee was... so strong.
Black and hot.
It reminded me of Adam and Steve,
not Adam and Eve.
Oh Steve.
Make her get up or
we are dead.
How long will this continue, Baani?
I mean, how long will this continue?
Let's go to a cafe,
grab a coffee.
Enjoy.
Jass, I'm not in the mood.
So let's get in the mood.
Siri, set the mood.
"Do the crazy dance!"
"Crazy, crazy, crazy dance."
- Come. Come.
- Go guys, have fun. Don't be too naughty.
Hey, Jass...
We'll go out. We'll go out.
- What are you doing?
- We'll go out. Wear this.
- Wear it. Wear it. Wear it.
- Jass.
This one. Wear this.
- I like it.
- Alright.
- Get ready quickly. I'll be right back.
- Okay, bye.
Where do I go?
Locked.
"When you're young..."
Kunnu, what the hell! Where is he?
- I'm asking. What are you--
- He's here.
You? Where are you coming from?
Toilet. Lavatory.
Bathroom. Washroom. Where else?
You are always so suspicious.
These girls I tell you...
Never mind, baby.
I think you're looking very good
- in my jacket.
- Really?
Come on, let's all three of us go out.
- Three? No, no. Please, not him.
- No, no.
You, me and Baani... I mean baby.
Yeah, baby's day out.
Baby's day out.
- Go out. Have food.
- Look at me. Don't look back.
- Look at me.
- Have fun. Bye.
Bye.
"My swaying veil..."
"Come touch my swaying veil, my love.
I won't tell a soul."
"I'm high on this youth of mine,"
"How do I take it down for you?"
"Let's go."
"My swaying veil..."
"She stole my peace, my sleep, my sanity,
took my senses and my strength as well."
"Floating like a kite, driving
me insane. What did she say?"
"My swaying veil..."
"Stole your peace, your sleep,"
"your sanity, stole your senses
and your strength as well."
"Floating like a kite,
driving you insane. What she said?"
"Sways carefree, tortures me cruelly."
"Touch her and she says..."
"Come touch my swaying veil, my love.
I won't tell a soul."
"This crazy lover's waiting at your door.
What do I do without you anymore?"
"My swaying veil..."
"Colours burst inside my heart,
I'm drenched in your love, my love,"
"The way it sways keeps telling me,
You're mine, only mine, my love,"
"The red veil you got
me from Lalbaug of Lalganj."
"My swaying veil..."
"Only for you, my love."
"You coloured it red with your love."
"My swaying veil..."
"Only for you, my love."
"Sways carefree, tortures me cruelly."
"Touch her and she says..."
"Come touch my swaying veil, my love.
I won't tell a soul."
"This crazy lover's
waiting at your door."
"What do I do without you anymore?"
"My swaying veil..."
You know, Preet,
this is my favourite cafe.
The weather is good.
It's outdoors.
- Thank you.
No worries.
By the way, when is your due date?
I'm actually in my third month.
So... six months.
- You?
- Halfway there.
Excuse me.
Father of my baby.
Hi, baby.
Are you here?
Yeah, I'm at the cafe. Come.
He's coming. How far is yours?
- My husband.
- Wow. What a coincidence.
Hello.
Where are you?
Oh... no problem.
See you in the evening.
Bye.
He's not coming?
Maybe next time.
- Hey...
Come.
Hi... Hello.
What's this?
Safety, girls... safety.
You must have seen on the road often...
No helmet, no safety.
For me? Yeah, my throat.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Baby, what are you doing?
Yeah.
- Preet, I'll leave.
- You see my helmet?
Oh, it was that guy
who took it over there.
He's not normally like this actually.
Thank you so much for coming, Preet.
- You guys continue...
- You pay the bill.
- What's the hurry?
- Let me get the bill.
- We'll take care of that.
- No, no... No chance.
- I'm taking care of this.
- Bye.
Let me pay please, Preet.
That's my helmet, wanker.
- No... not yet. I'll pay.
- No, I am paying.
- No, no, I need it.
- I'm gonna pay this time.
Let me keep it for some time.
I need it, you oaf.
- Come here.
- Back again?
That hurt? Didn't it?
Shit.
My leg. My bloody legs.
You saved my life, bro.
Here you go. Thank you.
Don't do it.
Your blunder has
put my gender in danger.
- Barbie shorts. Suits you.
- Shut up!
This Baani never locks the door.
She's back.
Big bag, bigger purse.
Jass, I think she's back
to live with you.
Kunnu, we should do two things.
- What?
- First, we should turn around.
- And then run.
- Yes. Come on.
Jass, my son.
- Mom!
Jass...
Mom?
- Mom's here. Mom's here.
Greetings, aunty.
Mom, I need you.
- So excited to see me?
- Yes.
Even I wasn't so excited
when you were born.
But mom, you didn't inform us
you'll be here.
You were never going to call me here.
Daughter-in-law, I got tired of
asking him when will I become a grandma.
Did you tell your mom about it?
Even I just found out.
Baani called me up and
gave me the good news.
She bought my ticket. Arranged my visa.
Hired a caretaker for the house.
She's my daughter,
not my daughter-in-law.
Bonding.
See, what I got for
my daughter from Punjab.
Sweets made of
dry fruit and fenugreek.
You could've sent it by courier.
You didn't have to come here, Mom.
Shut up.
These sweets are good
for you during pregnancy.
It's good for the mother and child.
Have it.
One, two, three, four, five...
Jass?
Seven...
Stealing in your own house?
Yes, I am.
Preet should also get these.
For her health and
the growth of her child.
I can't share my mother's love,
but I can share these sweets with her.
Let me help you.
Are you pregnant?
What about my growth?
They're for my children.
- Let me have one.
- Go take steroids.
- At least leave the jar behind.
- Get lost.
Sweets made of
dry fruit and fenugreek.
My mom sent these
from Punjab for Preet.
For the health of the
mother and growth of our baby.
How nice of them, right, Preet ma'am?
Brother... if Mom was alive,
she would've done this for me.
Preet. My mother is like your mother.
Excellent, Jass.
You said such a lovely thing.
In that case, call her here.
- Whom?
- Your mother.
- What an idea? Right?
- Guggi.
- Sire.
- Get his mother... a ticket.
- Yes.
- Thank you, brother.
Stop talking... about my mother.
Mom can't come here.
- Why?
We were born poor.
So, Mom looks after the house.
- Guggi.
- Yes, sire?
Send a few servants to his house.
There are many court
cases against Mom.
- She's a default--
- Guggi.
- Sire?
- Send a dozen lawyers as well.
- Sire.
- Anything else?
Our relatives...
We're not on good
terms with our relatives.
If Mom comes here,
they'll take over our land.
Should we send a dozen shooters?
Shooters?
- Shooters?
- No relatives, no fight.
- Brother.
- Anything else?
Hey, what happened, baby?
Everyone's talking about my mom,
but no one's asked about my dad.
My mom won't leave my dad alone
and come here.
- Dad...
- I understand baby, don't cry. Sit down.
That house is full of Dad's memories.
Mom can't come here
leaving them behind.
- Yeah, it's okay.
- No chance.
- Guggi...
- Sire?
- Book a chartered flight to India.
- Yes, sire.
Because we're going home,
to our motherland
and Jass' mother.
Amazing idea, brother.
You're the best.
Thank you so much.
You are so stubborn...
So stubborn.
You're really stubborn.
You just don't give up.
Instead of all of us going there,
Mom will come here.
My mom will come here.
"Toasted. Toasted. Toasted."
Kunnu. You called at the right time.
Why? What happened, Jass?
Randhawa wants to meet Mom.
Great. Serves you right for
stuffing her with mom's sweets.
- Sir, sugar?
- Leave.
- Okay, sir.
- How do I introduce them to Mom?
And where am I supposed
to find a fake mother?
Relax. Your Mom will be there.
We'll find you a mom
as good as your real mom.
I don't want a glimpse,
I want a full grown mother,
someone like old Nirupa Roy.
She'll come.
She'll come. She'll come.
"Mom... my dear Mom..."
"You're my darling child."
Sire, isn't she too
young to be his mother?
You asked for a mother...
and my mom's here.
Excellent. Delhi is for those
with a big heart, and London--
Let it be, Mom. Let it be.
Hello, Mr. Randhawa.
I got something for you.
You feel cold at night, don't you?
- A sweater, for you.
- How nice.
It will keep you warm.
- Thank you.
- Why are you standing at the back?
- You're his servant, aren't you?
- He is.
I can tell.
- Preet, my daughter-in-law.
- Hello, Mom.
This is for you.
- A picture of little Jass.
- Aww.
So cute.
- Alice, this dress is for you.
- Thank you.
I heard you take good
care of my daughter-in-law.
Strange. You know
everything about everyone.
She is my mother and
mothers know everything.
Right, brother?
Come, Mom. We'll continue
this conversation inside.
Let's go.
- Come.
- Let's go.
Brother, come.
How is your mother so young?
Shut up, Alice's lover.
Don't ask too many questions.
Even I have answers.
Sire. Sire. Sire.
Get lost.
He knows about my affair.
Mr. Kunnu, it's good to
have you back alone.
Did your psychotic friend leave UK--
What did I say? What did I bloody say?
I asked for someone mature,
like Nirupa Roy.
You sent me Mouni Roy.
So young!
Even Shah Rukh Khan
wasn't this young in 'Jawan'.
Sorry, Jass.
This was the best I could arrange
at such short notice.
But I'm sure she handled
everything perfectly, right?
Handled? Nonsense.
She walked in and said
"Delhi is for those with a big heart,
and London is for--"
I get it. I get it. Sorry.
- What if I'd got caught?
- Relax, Jass.
She's a professional.
Your fake mother will never be exposed.
- Really?
- No one.
- You sure?
- No one will catch on.
Hold on.
Sire, the "mother" Jass brought here...
isn't a mother.
She is an incredible person.
"Bhaiyyaji is never late..."
"Bhaiyyaji is never late,
to feed his wife and tuck her in..."
"And keeps the neighbour's
wife awake till morning."
"Tiptoes so she doesn't awake--"
She's popularly known
as Rasmalai Rajjo.
She has an entire series
of vulgar songs with weird names.
"And keeps the neighbour's
wife awake till morning."
Dilphek Doodhwali,
Makkhan Malishwali, Chikni Chupdi...
"...awake till morning."
My judgment was severely impaired.
Mistaking coal for a diamond...
and mud for a lotus.
Speak up, Jass's respected mother.
How do you explain this vulgarity?
All I want to say is...
I am not Jass's mother.
Sire!
Jass? What is Mom saying?
Jass will clarify
whatever needs clarifying.
- Jass!
- Yes, it's true. She's not my mother.
But before you pull out the gun,
hear me out first.
What is the entire story?
- Let me speak.
- Speak.
This goes back to when I was a child.
A small boy.
My real mother, Paramjeet, had a younger
sister Sharamjeet... aka Shammo.
This lady.
She was having an affair
with a guy called Shammi at that time.
When my mother found out
her sister was getting married,
she was overjoyed...
singing, dancing...
Do you know what was behind her?
Normally people talk about
what happened ahead.
Yes, but in this story,
what was behind her is more important.
While my mother was singing and dancing,
there was a long staircase behind her.
She slipped and fell--
Thud... thud... thud...
thud... thud... thud...
Next.
It was a long staircase. Hold on.
Thud... thud... thud...
thud... thud... thud...
Is she down yet?
No, my mother went up,
straight up to heaven.
I was very emotionally fragile.
I went to my aunt and said,
"Aunty, will you marry my dad?"
"Will you love this
child like his own mom?"
And without hesitation,
this great woman said 'yes'.
Ask... Ask her.
Help me. Stop taking footage.
Yes, I said yes.
I said, yes I will raise this child.
She is not educated.
She is completely illiterate.
She says wrong things
at the wrong time.
But she has a gift...
she can dance.
Yes.
With a heavy heart...
and flexible moves,
she became Rasmalai Rajjo.
Made videos for Tips, T-Series, Venus,
in order to raise me.
You showed me four
videos, I'll show you 40.
'Bangkok Mein Bhauchaal'
'Chunari mein Lugai'
'Ghagre Mein WiFi'
'Lollipop Lugai...'
'Choli ke Peeche Toli'
'Aunty Ke Peeche Bunty'
Enough!
Mom...
It's okay.
Wow!
Very touching, sir.
Please forgive me, Ms. Sharamjeet.
I misjudged you.
You turned out to be a goddess.
Epitome of motherhood.
What I did... wasn't by choice.
It was a single mother's helplessness.
Forgive me.
"It happens in this age,"
"You lose sleep and peace."
Sharamjeet, try this orange dress.
It will suit you.
And this lime colour...
will look even better on you.
But, Mr. Randhawa,
how can I accept all this?
And this white...
Marvellous.
This colour will look vibrant on you.
Shammo ji, so many dresses?
Are you taking them
to the laundry?
Mr. Randhawa told me try these on.
He personally chose them for me.
Brother-in-law.
Your mother is robbing my boss.
Why are you getting so irritated?
"Mom..."
Wow...
Mom?
"Mom... my dear Mom..."
- Mom!
- "You're my darling child."
- "I'm your darling child."
- Oh Mom!
Jass, just look at this. So cute, right?
Which one should we buy?
Blue or pink?
My dear wife, let's ask the
one who's going to wear it.
Junior, if you mind,
can I ask you something?
Which colour...
Excuse me. Baby product?
For my baby.
Everyone in London is becoming a father.
Brother-in-law? You here?
For my baby. Preet's baby.
Forget about me.
What are you doing here?
I was just...
My Guggudu...
Alice in Guggiland.
Alice is just my love...
Love may not satisfy hunger,
but it definitely leads to a baby bump.
And you can't control a horny.
Shall we give the good
news to Randhawa sir?
- No, no...
- No, I'll tell him.
- Brother-in-law...
- No, no...
let's keep this a secret.
Then pay my bill along with yours.
Done.
- I need this.
- Done.
Wet wipes.
But, Mr. Randhawa,
how can I accept this?
I am Jass's mother.
You did not give birth to Jass,
only raised him.
Shammo...
24-karat indium gold!
Guggi, why did she leave like this?
It's called values, boss.
No matter how mature a girl becomes,
whenever the topic
of her marriage comes up,
she gets embarrassed and runs away.
Sharamjeet,
what's going on in this house?
Do you know they--
Did Mr. Randhawa give you this?
It's a pre-wedding gift.
Son, I'm the mistress of this house now.
I'll do as I please, mister.
Preet. Preet. Control your brother.
He wants to marry my mother.
- Jass...
- What is he doing?
Jass, listen...
That's what I said. "Brother, listen".
After the marriage,
what will you call her?
Mother-in-law or sister-in-law?
And what are the kids going to call her?
Grandma or Aunty?
This will become that,
that will become this.
It will become a cocktail
of relationships.
Jass, listen to me.
At his age, he should
be blessings newly weds,
not planning his own wedding.
Jass, goddamnit, listen to me!
My water just broke.
This baby is coming now!
- Oh my God.
- Doctor. Call the doctor.
We need a doctor.
Calm down, baby. Calm down.
- Move.
- Oh my God.
Calm down, baby. Calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down!
- Okay.
- This is your fault.
- Sorry. I am sorry.
- Where are we going?
Fast.
Doctor, how can her water break
at just seven and a half months?
Wow, what a concerned father.
He takes such good care of her.
- Doctor.
- Yes, my dear?
What about me and the baby?
Don't worry.
I'll give you a painkiller.
I've got everything under control.
Please, everyone go out.
- I don't like overcrowded wards, please.
- Doctor?
- Yes, my dear?
- Can I please stay here?
- Excuse me?
- Please.
How are you related to her?
Well... I'm like her mother.
- Thank you.
- I'll be right back. One second.
Jass? Hey...
Why did I get four
missed calls from Mom?
Jass?
Mom?
I've been trying to call you.
Where've you been?
Why weren't you answering your phone?
- Mom, I was--
- Baani's labour pains have started.
I've brought her to the hospital.
Baani is here?
First, tell me what you are doing here?
I... Before I tell you my story,
tell me where Baani is.
- You okay?
- No!
- But I'm happy you're here.
- Me too.
Son. The doctor is saying
she can deliver today.
- Today?
- Yes.
And we must take good
care of her.
Yeah.
But you don't worry. Hold this.
Lord Ganesha will always be with us.
- And give me this phone.
- Give me back my phone, Mom.
- No. I won't...
- You did the right thing.
What an irresponsible father.
Come with me to the other room,
I'll show you a responsible father.
He never enters the room without a mask.
And look at him... terrible.
- He treats foreigners.
- Stop disturbing my patients and leave.
- Jass.
- Baani, I'll be right back.
Mom, my phone.
- Give it.
- Out. Out.
- Why doesn't he ever answer his phone?
- Again?
Why is everyone calling me?
- Where were you?
- I...was...
I've been calling for so long.
Not working.
The doctors are saying they'll
have to do a premature delivery,
and it has to be done today.
Today? Both of them?
What do you mean both of them?
Is there someone else?
When... a child is born,
a mother is also born.
So both.
Great. He's absolutely right.
The doctor's here.
Oh no.
Doctor, tell him about
Preet's premature delivery.
Why should I tell him?
Because he's the child's father.
He's the father of this child?
- Are you sure?
- Of course he is.
You must have seen him in a mask.
Look closely. Recognise him?
Same-same. I know him.
- Father and doctor have to talk.
- I recognise him.
- Father and doctor.
- Aren't you the same guy?
What did you say?
"Who's Your Daddy? Jumping with joy?"
I'll tell them everything.
- Mr. Randhawa...
- Dr. Gulati, emergency.
- What happened?
- Your patient is about to die.
- Hurry up or he will die.
- I'm coming back.
- I'm coming back. I'm coming back.
- We can't deliver a baby without a doctor.
I'm coming back.
Watch out. Hurry up.
How can I hurry up
when I'm sitting down?
Then hurry up while sitting down.
Where's the patient?
- Where's the patient?
- There is no patient, sir.
I lied to you.
- Because I had to tell you the truth.
- What truth?
Actually--
His truth.
He's not a bad guy,
he just kept getting stuck
in bad situations.
Selfie Kumar, he has two wives.
He's expecting two children.
It's a crime!
Doctor, Baani and Preet are in labour.
Preet will undergo a premature delivery.
I will tell them the truth,
but after the delivery is done.
I will deliver... you... to jail.
- I am going to expose this fraud!
- Please, doctor.
Out of my way--
Doctor, I cannot give
stress to both mothers.
- Move!
- Gulati.
Before you go out,
take a look at your own dirty deeds.
Look.
"Look aunt,
your boy's going astray."
"Stop teasing girls."
"I'll report you,
I'll get you arrested."
"I'll get you thrown in jail."
"Stop teasing girls."
Fake university doctor, get up.
Godamba! Godamba!
Doctor, which brand
of cheap tobacco is this?
Godamba is my wife's name.
If she finds out,
she'll beat me to a pulp.
I am married. I have two kids, please.
- And, even I am expecting babies.
- Two of them.
- You like reading books, don't you?
- Yes.
- Then you should read another book.
- Which one?
'Zindagi Jhandba Toh Muh Humesha Band Ba'
(When Life's A Train Wreck, You Better Zip It)
Otherwise you will become a widower.
Delivery. Please.
Breathe. Breathe.
Check where he is. Call him.
Give me your hand.
Call my husband. Out of the way.
Out of the way.
Lord Ganesha, first Baani came
in my life and then she left.
Then Preet came and so did Baani.
Lord Ganesha,
protect the mothers and the children.
Lord...
Who are you talking to, man?
Indian emotion. You won't understand.
I'm in deep trouble. Deep.
- Come on, push, push. You can do it.
- Jass, don't touch me.
- It's all because of you.
- Okay, sorry. Push, push.
You can do it.
Hallelujah, the baby's on its way.
It's a big baby.
I've got to check before I take it out.
- It's coming. It's coming.
- Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Congratulations, it's a girl.
With God's blessings,
I'm finally a grandma.
I had decided that if all went well,
I will go to Vaishno Devi
to seek blessings.
Mom...
Godamba. Godamba. Godamba.
Congratulations.
This time it's a boy.
- So sorry.
- Great.
Remember I told you, brother.
Uncle and nephew
swaying all over London.
Spinning... Spinning...
- Little Randhawa is here--
- What are you doing, Mr. Randhawa?
It's a hospital.
- Hold your gun.
- Brother.
Yes.
Even he looks like me.
I mean, only he looks like me.
Thank you again.
There's only two, right?
We'll go to India soon.
Jass, Mom and the baby
are in the parking lot, right?
Yes.
- Baani...
- What?
I forgot the files.
Call the elevator, I'll get them.
- Okay.
- Preet?
- Baani. Hi.
- How are you?
- Good. You delivered?
- Yes, baby girl. And you?
- Baby boy.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations to us.
- Lovely.
- Brother, my friend Baani.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Preet, my husband's coming.
- Just two minutes.
- Okay. Nice.
Now Preet isn't answering her phone.
- She will. Keep calling.
- And she complains I'm always busy.
Nothing you do is ever enough for them.
- Same story with me.
- Yes, Mom.
I'm coming. Baani's already downstairs.
Preet, that's my husband.
The father of my child.
Baani, you're joking, right?
He's the father of my child.
No, you are joking.
No, no, he's the father of my child.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Jass.
- Sire, do the honours.
Just a second,
Mr. Randhawa, I can explain.
- Actually by mistake--
- Rascal, what were you saying?
Growing love.
- Isn't that what he said?
- Yes.
No.
- What else did he say?
- I can't believe this.
- Nothing. What else did I say?
- Fraud.
- Oh yes.
- Stay away...
Nephew and uncle spinning in city.
- What else did you say?
- Sir, I thought you liked the song.
- Nothing.
Thud... Thud... Thud...
- Thud... Thud... Thud...
- Jass, how could you?
Thud... Thud... Thud...
You are Liar.
Head towards the exit.
Do not take the lift.
Baani, are you alright?
Stay calm. Please make it to the
nearest exit as soon as possible.
Head towards the exit.
Do not take the lift.
Are you okay?
Catch that rascal.
Don't let him escape.
Jass. Where are you going?
I want answers.
- Brother, Jass is running away.
- Jass... Catch him.
Who will save me in this situation?
I'd told you not to share your notes.
Disha, where is Mr. Godbole?
He must be in the classroom.
Oh God.
When someone's stressed,
my crazy heart says...
Come to Godbole. Come to Godbole.
Mr. Godbole...
What happened, Jass?
My classmates are bullying me.
So, I got scared and ran away.
You got scared? Oh God.
So innocent.
Now listen carefully
to what Godbole has to say.
Do you know what Gandhiji said?
A person's biggest enemy is his fear.
And what did Mandela say?
[gibberish]
What is Godbole uncle doing?
Mt. Kilimanjaro...
Control your fear, my friend.
There he is.
Hey...
Jass.
I'm ready.
Ask whatever you want.
- What have you done, Jass?
- How can you do this to us?
- You cheated on both of us.
- Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Baani, if you mind,
still can I ask you something?
You told me to move on and I moved on.
I found Preet and I fell in love.
And I'm the cheater?
You could have told us the truth.
How could I have told you the truth?
The doctor said you have complications.
I couldn't stress you out.
What choice did I have, Baani?
Why didn't you tell me
you were already married?
And that she's pregnant.
You're a bloody cheater!
Because our marriage was over.
Ask her. She ended it.
And I tried to tell you, Preet.
But every time I tried,
your brother showed up with his gun.
Betrayal... coffin...
- I didn't get the chance.
- What is he saying?
- Jass, please.
Hey, idiot.
Mr. Randhawa, I admit I lied.
I brought a fake mother.
But you started chasing
that fake mother too.
You're not young anymore,
but that's not stopping you.
And Shammo ji, the moment you got gold,
you switched sides.
Gold digger with a figure!
Hey, Jass. I admit I like gold...
but I like the guy
who gave it even more.
But Guggi has got the best choice.
Guggi, should I bust your balloons?
Mr. Randhawa, your house help Alice...
Alice and Guggi are... always at it.
- All night long.
- Guggi.
- Sire, I was going to tell you.
- What is he saying?
- No, no, please, sir. Please.
- The gun again.
Please don't shoot him.
- No, shoot him...
- I'm...
I am expecting his baby.
Why are you...
Great. One more.
Baby, no one will be here.
I'll make you happy.
Look, here comes the 12th man
of the losing team.
Dr. Gulati.
Enjoying your terrace break?
Godamba.
Godamba, his wife. We must tell her...
Forget it. He delivered both my kids.
Two? No, three.
I'm carrying your triplets, Dr. Gulati.
- What?
- Well done, doctor. Well done.
- Did you hear that?
- Three more.
Did you hear?
Moral of the story is -
when your own drawstrings are loose,
don't tug at others clothes.
You guys are...
- Jass, no...
- Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer. I will jump.
- I will jump.
- Jass, have you lost your mind?
Yes, you guys have driven my crazy.
I don't want any
sympathy or any apology.
- I am going.
- Don't behave like a kid, Jass.
Jass, think about the kids.
- I have only one regret.
- What?
My children will never
know their father's love.
- Hey!
- Jass, stop!
Don't just stand there. Do something.
- I'm jumping. I'm jumping.
- Jass...
Oh, my God. Please, Jass.
- Here I go.
- Jass, Jass...
- What do we do?
- Preet, he's your boyfriend.
I'm falling.
- He's your husband. Say something.
- Stop.
God, I'm coming.
Preet, Jass is a good guy.
I know, that's why I loved him and
had his baby, but he's also a liar.
I know he's a liar,
but his heart's in the right place.
Don't stop me, guys. I will jump.
What do you think, sire?
Is brother-in-law going to jump or fall?
I can jump any minute. Any minute now.
Save him, Gulati. He will fall down.
He's already fallen pretty low,
can't go any lower.
Selfie, come here.
Preet, just listen to me.
He's not a bad guy.
What are Baani and Preet
discussing about me?
I think they are fighting over you.
Both of them? Over me?
- Yes, both.
- I'm falling.
I have an idea.
You're already married to him.
You keep him.
He's my past. You keep him.
I'll move on. Don't worry. You keep him.
- Jass belongs to you.
- No, no, you are very nice.
Forgive him.
Husbands are like Gods. Keep him.
- You keep him!
- I said, you keep him!
- No, please keep him.
- Jass is yours.
You keep him. Keep him.
- Jass.
- Yes. Did you call me?
They've made a decision.
What?
- We both...
- You two?
- Don't want to live with you.
But I've done so much for you two.
How can you two leave me?
One of you can come with me.
I deserve one at least.
You two are cheaters.
I am being cheated.
I told you, the decision has been made!
Jass. Jass.
God's plan.
I've been to London, Paris...
even Japan.
But this my India, I love my India.
Two black coffees, girl.
To hell with your black coffee.
- Get me a beer.
- Okay.
Go ahead and drink it.
By the way, Jass.
Your life's such a mess.
They both left you.
So sorry to hear that, sir.
They both left you?
Yes, so what if they left me?
Will you fill in for them?
Will you take care of my two kids?
Control, sir. I have a boyfriend.
Jass. Relax.
Have faith in God.
He will do what's best.
Forget it.
If you mind still,
can I ask you something?
"When you're young..."
Who is using my line on me?
What's up... 10th grade backbencher
Jasswinder Ahuja?
Don't remember?
Mr. Shukla.
Mr. Godbole.
Mr. Mishra.
And always keep your
eye on Disha while running.
- Understood?
- Hi, Disha.
Wrong.
Come on.
- Disha?
- Finally.
- Hi.
I can't believe we're
meeting after all these years.
God's plan.
- I missed you, man.
- Me too.
Third?
First.
One second. Vishal.
Who is he?
- That's Vishal.
- He's so tall.
Vishal, meet Jass.
- Hey, man.
- My childhood friend.
Hi, man.
You were asking, who will
be best man at our wedding?
- Yeah.
- Wedding?
Who better than him?
He's my best friend from school.
Yeah...
Why only best man?
You can handle all the wedding rituals.
- Rituals?
- Yeah.
Can you sing?
Not just sing, he will dance as well.
- He's a terrific dancer.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Perfect.
That's amazing.
You'll do it, right?
Yeah...
Sorry. Mistake.
Okay, I'm going to
send you the invite, okay.
Yeah, don't be late.
Not at all,
I'll personally escort him there.
- That's amazing.
- We won't be late.
- See you, guys.
- So nice to see you.
Nice... hair.
- Bye.
Rascal... whenever
happiness knocked on my door,
- you always brought bad luck.
- What did I do?
- I can't find a single girl.
- You just got dumped by two.
- Why you--
- You won't find any girl...
Calm down. Calm down.
Look at your face.
I was joking. It was just a prank.
And that tall guy Vishal?
Vishal is just a friend.
In fact, he's like a brother to me.
Brother? I like brothers.
- I got you, right?
- You got me.
- So...
- So?
Are you...
single?
Yeah, I am... single.
And you?
Fully single.
- That's great.
- I know that is.
- So, then...
- I think we...
Tell her that you have two--
Two?
Let's go there for two minutes.
- Sure.
- There.
- You first.
- Thanks.
"When you're young, love happens."
At least tell her that
you have two kids in London!
"When you apply kohl in your eyes,"
"Boys look at you and say 'wow.'
"Like a peacock, wherever you walk,"
"Boys look at you and say 'wow.'"
"Billo, there's no one
like you on this earth,"
"Truly, in the whole world
there's no match for your beauty."
"Oh beautiful one, the grace
and sway that your body has,"
"Honestly, there is no
such bend on the map of earth."
"Slowly, gently sway your waist,"
"Have a little mercy on the boys,"
"Don't let your blue eyes
create such havoc,"
"Don't ignite us with your hotness."
"When you apply kohl in your eyes,"
"Boys look at you and say 'wow.'
"Like a peacock, wherever you walk,"
"As if made in Italy,"
"Those eyes are like bullets"
"And fire shots at heart."
"You are like a glass statue."
"Seeing your beauty"
"Everyone is jealous."
"Yesterday you went to
Patiala to buy a nose ring,"
"How many lakhs did you spend on Gucci?"
"Top models may try
to compete with you,"
"But there is no match for you."
"Get a red dress stitched
and will suit you well."
"Wear a Punjabi Jutti
with a small bells"
"Give us orders openly."
"And let our hearts
connect with each other."
"When you apply kohl in your eyes,"
"Boys look at you and say 'wow.'"
"Like a peacock, wherever you walk,"
"My eyes are rosy."
"They are intoxicating."
"I have made people yearn."
"My wrists are fair."
"I create havoc."
"My waist causes devastation. Oh, oh!"
"Someone calls me queen of
flowers and some call me butterfly."
"Some say I am
like lightning in the sky."
"Whosoever looks at my beauty
calls me prettier than angels."
"Make such a dance
step that goes viral."
"Get a song written by Gill Roy."
"Dance with heels to the tune."
"Don't feel shy standing far."
"When you apply kohl in your eyes,"
"Boys look at you and say 'wow.'"
"Like a peacock, wherever you walk,"
"Wow!"